He's dying to save mankind.
Mickey 17 is a science fiction, comedy, adventure film directed by Bong Joon Ho.
Unlikely hero Mickey Barnes finds himself in the extraordinary circumstance of working for an
employer who demands the ultimate commitment to the job… to die, for a living.
Mickey Barnes, played by Robert Pattinson.
Nasha, played by Naomi Ackie.
Timo, played by Steven Yeun.
Kenneth Marshall, played by Mark Ruffalo.
Ylfa, played by Toni Collette.
Kai Katz, played by Anamaria Vartolomei.
Mickey 17 is a 2025 science fiction black comedy film written, produced, and directed
by Bong Joon Ho, based on the 2022 novel Mickey7 by Edward Ashton.
The film stars Robert Pattinson in the title role, alongside Naomi Ackie, Steven Yeun, Patsy Ferran, Cameron
Britton, Daniel Henshall, Stephen Park, Anamaria Vartolomei, Toni Collette, and Mark Ruffalo.
Set in the year 2054, the plot follows a man who joins a space colony voyage as an
"Expendable", a disposable worker who is cloned every time he dies.
The film differs from the novel, meaning that the novel's sequel,
Antimatter Blues, cannot be adapted into a film.
Mickey 17 had its world premiere at Leicester Square in London on February
13, 2025, and was released theatrically by Warner Bros.
Pictures in South Korea on February 28, and in the United States on March 7.
The film received generally positive reviews from
critics and grossed $133 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, dark
comedy, space travel, space colony, alien planet.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.